

Ferdinand FelixWeb Developer

Phone: 62 851-5730-8533
Email: felixhermawan@gmail.com
Website: yaelahfelix.vercel.app
Github: yaelahfelix
Linked In: Ferdinand Felix

I am a programmer with experience in various programming languages and technologies. With strong leadership skills, I have successfully led teams in developing innovative and effective technology projects. I am committed to continuous learning and adapting to the latest technological advancements.

EXPERIENCE

Feb 2024 - Present Fullstack Web Developer

Ability Online Academy - PT Eminen Karya Indonesia

I am interning in this company as a Fullstack Developer at the education technology company. Ability Online Academy, developing a learning website for school students. I have an important role in this development, the technologies used and mastered in this development are ReactJS, Laravel, TailwindCSS,Material UI.

Feb 2023 - Present Freelance Web Developer

As a freelance web developer, I have successfully completed numerous projects leveraging the powerful capabilities of Next.js, Laravel, and React. My work involves creating dynamic and responsive web applications that meet client specifications and

industry standards

Jan 2023 - May 2023 Office Administrator

PT Tuv Nord Indonesia

As an Office Administrator, my responsibilities include managing inventory by recording incoming and outgoing goods, creating and maintaining data records, and handling customer phone calls. These tasks ensure smooth office operations and accurate inventory management, while also providing excellent customer service.

Education

2024 - Present Universitas BSI (BSI University)

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology (BSIT)

Recipient of a Fully Funded Scholarship to study at BSI University

2024 - Present **HEROS Language Center**

Japanese Language JLPT N4

Recipient of a Fully Funded Scholarship to study Japanese at JLPT

N4 Level

2021 - 2024 SMKS Bina Nasional Informatika (High School)

Network And Computer Engineering

Top Graduate of Vocational High School Chairman Of Student Councol for a year

HIGHLIGHT PROJECT

January 2024

Si-Pintar BNI (Exam Application)

Project Manager, Fullstack Web Developer, React Native

I contributed to the development of a school examination application using Next.js and React Native. This project aimed to facilitate online exams for students, providing a seamless and secure experience across web and mobile platforms. By leveraging Next.js, I ensured optimal performance and SEO-friendly features for the web application, utilizing server-side rendering (SSR) and static site generation (SSG). For the mobile application, I employed React Native to deliver a consistent cross-platform experience Android users.

Feb 2023 - June 2023

Gobot.id

Front End Developer (Next.JS)

Gobot is a bot service aimed at SME traders to serve customers. I am a part of this project, specifically as the Front End developer using Next JS. In this project, I utilize Material UI and Tailwind CSS for styling. I also create interactive UI by fetching data from the database and adhering to the provided UI/UX Engineer's design. Additionally, I implement an authentication system for users. There are also many complex JavaScript logic components utilized in this project.

SKILLS

Programming

Javascript, Typescript, SQL, Linux, NextJS, Laravel, React JS, Material UI, TailwindCSS, PHP, Python, Laravel, Node JS, Vue JS, Svelte, AI

Soft Skills

Leadership, Problem Solving, Communication, Adaptability, Public Speaking Communication, Time Managemenet

Others

Design, Photography, Excel, Word, Powerpoint, Video Editing

VOLUNTEER

August 2023 - August 2024

Chairman

Student Council (OSIS) SMKS Bina Nasional Informatika
Led school events and community service projects, enhancing leadership and organizational skills.

ACHIVEMENTS

May 2024	Top Graduate of Vocational High Scholl SMKS Bina Nasional Informatika
May 2024	Recipient of a Fully Funded Scholarship for Study at Japanese Language at JLPT N4 Level Heros Language Center
Feb 2024	Recipient of a Fully Funded Scholarship for Study at BSI University Universitas BSI